

Summary

San Francisco based UX designer utilizing my past experiences and newly developed design skills to produce data-driven functionality and aesthetically pleasing solutions.

Recent Projects

Fruition Brewing | Web page re-design of breweries website

- UX, Research, Information Architecture and Web Design
- www.fruitionbrewing.com (website built based on re-design using Wix in order to give client control)

Newlocal | Location-based iOS application

- Lead designer, UX, Branding, Research, Information Architecture, Prototype and Testing
- View InVision prototype

Experience

Uber ATG | Engineering Operations Technician

Aug. 2016 - Present

- Defined requirements and criteria to drive decisions regarding a connected worker solution to increase efficiency or the R&D technician team
- Data analysis and platform triage leading to improved troubleshooting processes which helped drive hardware engineering development

Ottomotto LLC. | Engineering Operations Technician

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016 (acquired by Uber Aug. 2016)

- Assisted with truck retrofit and helped develop a truck-build inventory system using QR codes to ensure repeatable and safe builds of self-driving trucks
- Managed a small team that annotated and QC'd images which lead to decreased development time of our perception system
- Analyzed potential acquisition of a company that would be able to replace our labeling workforce/needs

Google Inc. | Program Manager - Operations (Self-Driving Cars) June 2012 - Dec. 2015

- Coordinated and managed the logistics and documentation of various tests for onboard engineering, systems engineering, mechanical engineering, UX, public relations/marketing, and business development
- Helped run and develop procedures for conducting UX studies for various aspects of the self-driving car
- Played a key role in designing our training mechanisms that were used to grow the self-driving car operations team to over 100 contractors, while maintaining the highest level of safety

nicolasmunley.com (415) 810 - 3223 nrmunley@gmail.com

Skills

Visual Design
UX/UI Design
Project Management
User Research & Testing
Brand Strategy & Identity
Information Architecture
Personas & User Stories
Wireframing & Prototyping
Agile and Scrum

Programming Skills

Working Knowledge

HTML CSS

Basic Knowledge

JavaScript SQL

Linux

CSS Grid

Tools

Adobe Creative Suite

Sketch

Figma

InVision

Usability Hub

GitHub

Maze

Typeform

Marvel App

Education

Bloc | UX/UI Design and Development Apprenticeship | Feb. 2017 - Aug. 2018

CSU Chico | BS Civil Engineering | Aug. 2005 - May. 2010



